one of the tools that you'll be using
您将使用的工具之一
the most while painting is the color
绘画中最重要的是色彩
selector I prefer to use the artistic
选择器 我更喜欢用艺术性的
color selector set to the HSI or hsy
颜色选择器设置为HSI或HSY
modes because they better represent
模式 因为它们更好地代表了
natural color but there are others to
自然的颜色 但还有其他颜色
choose from like the classic HSV mode
从Like经典HSV模式中选择
the artistic color selector features a
艺术型颜色选择器具有
circle that allows you to select a pure
允许您选择纯净的圆圈
color blue yellow red magenta green and
颜色为蓝色、黄色、红色、洋红色、绿色和
so on along with the saturation or
因此 随着饱和度或
intensity of the color currently I am
我目前的颜色强度
using the HSI color mode so on the left
使用HSI颜色模式 因此在左侧
is a strip that shows the value or
是显示值的条带或
brightness of the color if I choose the
颜色亮度(如果我选择
wide gamut color selector this is closer
宽色域颜色选择器 更接近
to what you'd see in most other art apps
你在大多数其他艺术应用程序中看到的东西
now the Hue is on the outer ring and the
现在色调在外环上
saturation and brightness are expressed
表示饱和度和亮度
in a diamond shape moving left to right
在一个从左向右移动的钻石形状中
controls the saturation and up and down
控制饱和度和上下
controls the brightness it's also
控制亮度 它也是
possible to control Hue saturation and
可以控制色相饱和度和
brightness with individual sliders
单个滑块的亮度
moving the sliders also affects the
移动滑块也会影响
color selector so if I move the Hue
颜色选择器 所以如果我移动色调
slider you can see the Hue ring moving
滑块你可以看到色调环在移动
in response I can also use the
作为响应 我还可以使用
saturation slider to make the color more
饱和度滑块可使颜色更丰富
vibrant or more muted the third slider
第三个滑块充满活力或更柔和
controls the brightness which can be
控制亮度 它可以
used to make the color lighter or darker
用来使颜色变浅或变暗
and the fourth slider controls both the
第四个滑块控制两个
saturation and brightness together to
饱和度和亮度一起达到
get a more natural lightening or
得到一个更自然的闪光或
darkening you can preview the color you
变暗你可以预览你的颜色
have selected in the color swatch in the
中的色样中选择了
top left of the color selector in order
颜色选择器的左上角按顺序
to select a color you can follow my
要选择一种颜色 可以按照我的
three-step process first think about the
三步流程首先考虑
Hue of the color you want if I were
如果我是你想要的颜色的色调
going to paint a daytime Sky then I'd
去画一幅白天的天空 然后我会
choose a color somewhere in between
选择介于两者之间的颜色
Indigo and cyan step two is to decide
Indigo和Cyan第二步是决定
how light or dark I want the sky to be
我希望天空有多亮或多暗
I'll choose a blue that's bright for
我要选一种颜色鲜艳的蓝色
step three I will decide how saturated
第三步 我将决定饱和程度
to make the color is it going to be an
为了做这个颜色 它会是一个
overcast day and kind of muted or is it
阴天 有点阴沉 还是
going to be a bright sunny day and very
将是一个阳光明媚的日子 非常
vibrant let's say it's going to be a
我们可以说 这将是一场
bright sunny day so I will choose a
晴朗的一天 所以我会选择一个
saturated blue to recap I chose CH my
总而言之 我选择了CHMY
Hue first I chose my value second and I
色调第一 我选择我的价值 第二 我
chose my saturation third step number
选择我的饱和度第三步数
two and three are interchangeable so it
两个和三个可以互换 所以它
doesn't really matter which property you
并不重要的是你拥有哪一处房产
choose first in fact you can choose both
先选事实上你可以两个都选
value and saturation at the same time if
值和饱和度 如果
you're using the wide gamut color
您使用的是宽色域的颜色
selector or hue and saturation together
选择器或色调和饱和度一起使用
if you're using the artistic color
如果你使用的是艺术色彩
selector I'll fill my canvas with that
选择器 我会用它填满我的画布
blue color I'll also show the entire
蓝色 我也会展示整个
canvas next if I want to add a bright
画布下一步如果我想再添一抹亮色
yellow sun in the sky I'll select yellow
天空中的黄色太阳 我会选择黄色
for my hue and then obviously we don't
对于我的色调 很明显我们不是
want a dark Sun or a dull Sun so the
我想要一个黑暗的太阳还是暗淡的太阳
color we choose needs to be bright and
我们选择的颜色需要鲜艳和
saturated I'll choose a color for my sun
我要为我的太阳选择一种颜色
and then paint with the airbrush soft to
然后用喷枪轻轻地喷漆
add it in another way to quickly select
以另一种方式添加以快速选择
a color is to use the pop-up panel you
一种颜色是使用弹出式面板
can access this whenever the brush tool
无论何时使用画笔工具都可以访问它
is selected by right clicking on the
通过右击
canvas the center is a color
画布中心是一种颜色
selector that covers the basics of
选择器 该选择器涵盖
selecting color in CR we will be going
我们将在CR中选择颜色
more in- depth into color selection
更深入地了解颜色选择
later in this course now let's discuss
在本课程的后面部分 现在让我们讨论
how to use undo and redo undo can remove
如何使用撤消和重做撤消可以删除
brush strokes and other operations one
画笔笔画等操作之一
at a time redo can bring them back if I
在某个时候 重做可以把他们带回来 如果我
start drawing a series of lines
开始绘制一系列线条
emanating from the Sun with airbrush
用喷枪从太阳发出
soft I can go to edit undo and each time
软我可以去编辑撤销和每次
I do this one more brush jerk will be
我做这件事的时候会再有一个笨蛋
removed until I reach my undo limit a
删除 直到达到我的撤消限制a
faster way to undo is to press contrl Z
撤消的快速方法是按Ctrl Z键
on your keyboard you can redo with
在你的键盘上 你可以重做
control shift Z as I mentioned there is
控制移位Z 正如我所提到的
a limit to how many undos you can use
您可以使用的撤消次数限制
you can find this setting under General
您可以在常规下找到此设置
miscellaneous if I draw a lot of lines
如果我画了很多线 那就麻烦了
and then I try to undo them all I'm
然后我试着把它们全部撤销我是
going to eventually reach my limit by
最终会达到我的极限
default the maximum is 200 but your
默认最大值为200 但您的
system may only be able to handle fewer
系统可能只能处理更少的
undos than that that's enough to go back
比这更糟 那就足够回去了
quite a ways but if I made more than 200
有很大的差距 但如果我赚了200多
lines I wouldn't be able to go past that
台词 我不能超过它
I'll go ahead and set my undue limit to
我将继续将我不适当的限制设置为
32 since that will free up Computer
32 因为这将释放计算机
Resources and I hardly ever use more
资源 我几乎从来没有用过更多的资源
than that another limitation is that
除此之外 另一个限制是
undo and redo information is cleared
撤消和重做信息已清除
when once you close a document or the
当您关闭文档或
cre application rather than use the
CRE应用程序而不是使用
keyboard for undo and redo you can also
用于撤消和重做的键盘您也可以
use the welome tablet properties to set
使用Welome绘图板属性来设置
one of your Express keys or your touch
您的某个快捷键或您的触摸
ring to execute these
执行这些命令的环
shortcuts now let's discuss erasing and
快捷键现在让我们讨论一下擦除和
cre one way to erase brush Strokes from
消除笔刷笔划的一种方法
your canvas is to select any eraser
你的画布是选择任何橡皮擦
brush there is an erasers category I'll
刷子有一类橡皮 我会的
start with eraser soft the erasers work
从橡皮擦软开始橡皮擦起作用
similarly to a real world eraser lighter
类似于现实世界中的橡皮打火机
pressure results in a thinner softer
压力会导致更薄更柔软
erasing firmer pressure gradually
逐渐抹去更坚挺的压力
removes everything the Eraser tool can
删除橡皮擦工具可以删除的所有内容
erase any of the categories of media
擦除任何介质类别
because the canvas I am painting on is
因为我在画布上画的是
blue that is what I get when I erase if
蓝色 这就是我擦除的结果 如果
I change the background color to
我将背景颜色更改为
something else I'll get that instead
其他的 我要买那个
there are other brush variants that can
还有其他画笔变体可以
be used to modify the shape and behavior
用于修改形状和行为
of your eraser for example there are
例如 你的橡皮擦有
hard Edge square and textured erasers
硬边正方形和纹理橡皮
just like with the brushes that apply
就像使用适用的画笔一样
paint there are properties to change the
绘制有一些属性可以更改
brush size an opacity of the Eraser so
笔刷调整橡皮擦的不透明度 以便
if I want an eraser that erases slowly I
如果我想要一块擦得很慢的橡皮
can set the opacity lower now the Eraser
现在可以降低橡皮擦的不透明度
takes time to build up and erase
需要时间来建立和删除
completely it is also possible to create
完全有可能创造出
your own erasers that can be customized
您自己的可定制的橡皮
to erase with texture and other brush
使用纹理和其他笔刷擦除
properties but we will take a look at
属性 但我们将查看
how to do that a little bit later you
你过一会儿怎么做呢？
can also toggle any brush to become an
还可以将任何画笔切换为
eraser with the keyboard shortcut of E
使用键盘快捷键E的橡皮擦
when you press it again you will return
当你再按一次它时 你会返回
to the normal brush Behavior this makes
对于正常的画笔行为 这将使
it really easy to quickly switch between
可以很容易地在
AAS Ing and painting there's also an
在绘画和绘画中还有一个
icon for this in the properties bar the
属性栏中的图标
pen included with your drawing tablet
绘图板附带的钢笔
might also have an eraser on the back
背面可能还有一块橡皮
end the walkom proen does once I flip
一旦我翻转 结束Walkom Proen所做的
the pen over and tap on the tablet crto
把笔转过来 轻敲平板电脑
will recognize it you can select an
将识别它 您可以选择一个
eraser brush with the Eraser end of the
橡皮刷用橡皮擦的一端
pen and now when you use that end of the
笔 现在当您使用
pen you'll erase flip the pen back over
笔你要擦掉 把笔翻过来
to return to drawing cre has basically
返回到绘图cre基本上已经
assigned two different brushes to your
将两个不同的画笔分配给您的
pen just like the drawing end the Eraser
笔就像画结束的橡皮擦
end of the pen is pressure sensitive so
笔尖是压敏的 所以
I can erase lightly with light pressure
我可以用轻微的压力轻轻地擦掉
or I can erase more thoroughly with
或者我可以更彻底地用
heavy pressure I don't really use the
压力太大了 我不是真的用
Eraser on my pen for erasing that often
我笔上的橡皮擦 因为我经常擦掉
nor do I really erase that much because
我也不会真的擦掉那么多因为
there are lots of other ways you can
有很多其他方法可以让你
remove marks or fix mistakes which we
删除标记或修复我们
will discuss later in these lessons if
我将在这些课程的后面部分讨论
your pen does not have an eraser like
你的钢笔没有橡皮擦
the pro pen 3 then you will have to set
专业钢笔3 然后你将不得不设置
one of your pen buttons to erase now if
如果出现以下情况 请立即擦除其中一个笔按键
I hold down this button on my pen it
我按住了钢笔上的这个按钮
temporarily activates the eraser tool if
在以下情况下临时激活橡皮擦工具
I let go of the button then I can draw
我松开按钮 然后我就可以画了
again I prefer to keep one button set to
同样 我更喜欢将一个按钮设置为
resize the brush with shift and the
使用Shift键和
other to rightclick so I will set them
要右键单击的其他项 以便我将设置它们
back one thing that is also useful about
回顾一下同样有用的一件事
the Eraser end of your pen is that you
你钢笔的橡皮擦一端是你
can use it to select something other
可以使用它来选择其他内容
than the Eraser for example you can
以橡皮擦为例 你可以
choose to have the Eraser and select a
选择拥有橡皮擦并选择一个
blender or paintbrush rather than erase
搅拌器或画笔 而不是擦除
simply tap on the canvas with the Eraser
只需用橡皮擦轻拍画布
end then use it to select a different
结束 然后使用它选择不同的
brush you can even use the Eraser end to
你甚至可以用橡皮擦来刷
Pan the canvas with space bar and change
用空格键平移画布并更改
the brush size while holding shift I'll
按住Shift键的同时显示画笔大小
leave it up to you to decide whether you
让你来决定你是不是
prefer to blend or erase with your
更喜欢混合或擦除您的
eraser and I blend more than I erase so
橡皮擦和我混合的比我擦掉的更多所以
I'll reserve it for blending the Eraser
我要把它留着用来混合橡皮擦
tool can be fully customized with
工具可通过以下工具完全定制
various brush properties you can choose
可以选择的各种画笔属性
from a wide range of different brush
从各种不同的画笔
tips and you can add spacing and other
提示 您可以添加空格和其他
properties now this is a more
现在这是一个更多的
interesting looking eraser I'd of course
看起来很有趣的橡皮 我当然会
want to save this custom eraser if I
如果我想保存此自定义橡皮擦
want to keep it but we'll look at how to
我想留着它 但我们会看看如何
do that later in this
稍后将在本文中执行此操作
course next let's take a look at how to
接下来 让我们来看看如何
sample colors I'll go to file open and I
样本颜色我会打开文件 然后我
will load the sampling template you can
将加载采样模板 您可以
find these in the artwork and templates
在图稿和模板中找到这些
folder and the course resource files a
文件夹和课程资源文件作为
simple way to keep your colors
保持色彩的简单方法
consistent throughout your artwork is to
在你的艺术作品中贯穿始终的是
sample colors that have already been
已创建的示例颜色
applied to your canvas to do that you
应用到你的画布上 这样做你
can select the sample color tool and
可以选择样例颜色工具和
then click on a color on screen to
然后点击屏幕上的一种颜色
activate it in the color selector if I
如果我在颜色选择器中激活它
sample a color and then select a brush
对颜色进行采样 然后选择画笔
like the basic five size opacity
像基本的五个大小的不透明度
paintbrush I am able to paint with the
我可以用画笔来画画
sampled color rather than selecting the
采样颜色 而不是选择
sample color tool with the brush tool
使用画笔工具对颜色工具进行采样
selected you can activate the sample
选中后 您可以激活样本
color tool at any time by holding down
通过按住鼠标左键随时使用颜色工具
alt on your keyboard by default control
键盘上的Alt键默认控制
is the keyboard shortcut for this but I
是这个的键盘快捷键 但我
have changed it since most other art
已经改变了它 因为大多数其他艺术
apps use alt if you didn't install my
如果您没有安装我的应用程序 请使用Alt
custom keyboard shortcuts you can change
您可以更改的自定义键盘快捷键
this manually or leave it set to control
手动设置或将其设置为控制
when you release the shortcut you will
当您释放快捷键时 您将
return to the brush tool that's really
返回到画笔工具 这真的是
the quickest and easiest way to sample
最快捷、最简单的取样方法
color while you're painting if you
在你绘画的时候上色 如果你
prefer you can also activate the sample
首选您还可以激活样品
color tool using an Express key or a
使用快捷键或
button on your pen by default the sample
默认情况下 笔上的按钮示例
size is one pixel so occasionally the
大小是一个像素 所以有时
color you get may not be what you expect
你得到的颜色可能不是你想要的
especially if you're sampling on a busy
尤其是如果你是在一个忙碌的
image these pixels are very small and
图像中这些像素非常小
very close together so it's difficult to
离得很近 所以很难
pick the same color twice it is possible
同样的颜色挑两次是有可能的
to sample a larger area to average the
要对更大的区域进行采样 以平均
colors but we will discuss us how to do
颜色 但我们会讨论如何做
that a little bit later when sampling
在抽样时稍晚一点
you get a preview of the sampled color
您将获得采样颜色的预览
in a Swatch next to your cursor now
现在在光标旁边的样例中
let's move on to discuss some of the
让我们继续讨论一些
basics of saving your artwork I'll make
拯救你的艺术品的基础 我会做的
some Modern Art and let's say that I
一些现代艺术 比方说我
want to save this I'll go to the file
想要保存这个 我会转到文件
menu and I can choose either save or
菜单 我可以选择保存或
save as I prefer to use save as because
另存为我更喜欢使用另存为 因为
it allows me to save iterations of my
它允许我保存我的
work rather than save over a single
工作而不是存钱
document there is a function for
文档有一个函数 用于
iterative saving in cre but I like to
迭代保存在cre中 但我喜欢
just save iterations manually after
只需在以下情况下手动保存迭代
choosing save I'll select a location
选择保存 我将选择一个位置
where I'll be able to find this file
在那里我可以找到这份文件
then I'll give my file a name I'm going
然后我会给我的文件起一个我要去的名字
to call it test save and then I'll
将其称为测试保存 然后我将
choose a file format the default file
选择默认文件的文件格式
format for cre is KRA and it will
Cre的格式是kra 它将
preserve any proprietary cre layers or
保留任何专有的cre层或
features it's recommended that you save
建议您保存的功能
the original copies of your artwork as
您的艺术作品的原始副本
C.K to ensure full compatibility that's
C.K以确保完全兼容 这是
not to say you cannot work between Crea
并不是说你不能在Crea之间工作
and Photoshop or other art applications
和Photoshop或其他艺术应用程序
using the cross compatible PSD file
使用交叉兼容的PSD文件
format because you can but be aware that
格式 因为您只能意识到
there are certain layer features that
有些特定的图层要素
are proprietary to cre and are not
是cre专有的 而不是
compatible with the PSD file format you
兼容您的PSD文件格式
also have the option of saving as PNG
我还可以选择另存为PNG
jpeg Tiff and tons of other formats some
JPEGTiff和许多其他格式
of these formats can be very helpful for
这些格式中的任何一种都对
printing or posting on the web but we
打印或在网上发布 但我们
will come back to that what's important
会回到那个重要的问题上来
is that you always save your original
你总是保存你的原件
working file as a layered format such as
分层格式的工作文件 如
Creed K Photoshop PSD or tip if the
Creed K Photoshop PSD或TIP
other file formats will flatten your
其他文件格式将使您的
image and discard the individual layers
对各个层进行成像并丢弃
we haven't really talked very much about
我们真的没怎么谈过
the importance of layers but you'll be
层次分明的重要性但你会
using them a lot later in the course
在后面的课程中会用到很多东西
addition to saving your original copy
除了保存您的原始副本
you may also want to create additional
您可能还希望创建其他
copies of your work in other formats and
您的作品的其他格式和副本
sizes a quick way to do this is to
要做到这一点 一种快捷的方法是
select export rather than save if you're
如果要执行以下操作 请选择导出而不是保存
planning to print your work saving as a
计划将您的工作保存打印为
tiff will give you the highest image
TIFF会给你最高的形象
quality while preserving the layers in
质量 同时保留中的层
your image I've already already saved my
你的形象我已经保存了我的
original as a KRA so now I'll export to
作为KRA的原件 所以现在我将导出到
save a copy as a tiff and name it test
将副本另存为TIFF并将其命名为TEST
save print if you're saving your artwork
如果要保存图稿 请保存打印内容
to the web then you'll want to choose
到网上 然后你会想要选择
PNG jpeg or possibly webp personally I
PNG jpeg或可能的WebP个人i
prefer PNG because it uses lossless
首选PNG 因为它使用无损
compression meaning that it's not going
压缩意味着它不会
to degrade the quality of your image in
在中降低图像质量的步骤
order to make the file size smaller PNG
以使文件大小更小PNG
also supports transparent backgrounds
还支持透明背景
the jpeg format will produce a smaller
Jpeg格式将产生一个较小的
file size but it may degrade the quality
文件大小 但可能会降低质量
of your image by throwing away some
通过扔掉一些你的形象
image and color details jpeg does not
图像和颜色细节jpeg不能
support background transparency and will
支持背景透明度 并将
fill the background with white so only
仅用白色填充背景
use jpeg if you must otherwise choose
如果必须选择jpeg 请使用jpeg
PNG I'll select the PNG format and I'll
我将选择PNG格式 然后我将
name the file test save web then I'll
将文件命名为TEST SAVE WEB 然后我将
save it when saving copies you may also
在保存副本时保存它您也可以
want to resize your image but we'll
想要调整您的图像大小 但我们会
discuss how to do that later in this
在本文的后面讨论如何做到这一点
course if I look in the folder where I
当然 如果我查看我所在的文件夹
saved those images I have my original
保存了那些图像 我有我的原件
copy and K format which which preserves
复制和保留的K格式
the layers and the original detail of my
我的作品的层次感和原始细节
artwork then I have a highquality tiff
艺术品 然后我有一个高质量的口角
that I can print from and a PNG that I
我可以从中打印的PNG和我
can post to the web I'll return to cre
我可以在网上发帖 我会回到cre的
in my opinion the best way to save is to
在我看来 最好的省钱方法是
use iterative saving iterative saving is
使用迭代保存迭代保存为
the process of saving sequential copies
保存顺序拷贝的过程
of your artwork this can be a great way
对于你的艺术品来说 这是一种很好的方式
to minimize risk while painting because
在绘画时将风险降至最低 因为
you'll always have an older version to
您将始终有一个较旧的版本可供
go back to if you make a major mistake
如果你犯了一个重大错误 请回到
it's also useful to show the progress of
它还有助于显示
a painting there is a save incremental
一幅画在那里有一个保存增量
version function in CR which will
CR中的版本函数 它将
automatically add a number to the file
自动向文件中添加数字
name each time you save but to do it
每次存钱时都说出名字 但要这么做
manually just choose save as and then
手动只需选择另存为 然后
add a number or other type of
添加号码或其他类型的
descriptive label CR does offer an
描述性标签CR确实提供了
autosave feature the options can be
自动保存功能选项可以是
found in general file handling you can
在一般的文件处理中发现您可以
change the frequency and quantity of
更改频率和数量
saves or deactivate it alog together you
将其保存或停用为您一起记录
can even unhide the autosave files from
甚至可以将自动保存的文件从
your file explorer if you like
您的文件资源管理器 如果您喜欢
organizing your files is is an essential
整理您的文件是必不可少的
Habit to adopt especially if you create
养成习惯 特别是如果你创造了
artwork without proper organization it
没有适当组织的艺术作品
can be easy for you to lose your work
对你来说很容易丢掉工作
due to forgetting where it was saved
因为忘记了它被保存在哪里
accidental deletion or overwriting to
意外删除或覆盖到
avoid this it's best to stay organized
避免这种情况 最好保持井然有序
from the start because trying to sort
从一开始就是因为尝试排序
through a disorganized collection of
通过一个杂乱无章的
artwork later will be timec consuming
稍后的艺术作品将耗费Timec
and tedious create a folder or select a
单调乏味地创建文件夹或选择
hard drive that's dedicated to your
专为您提供的硬盘
artwork if it helps create subfolders by
如果图稿有助于通过以下方式创建子文件夹
year or month and then by project name
年或月 然后按项目名称
what's important here is that you're
这里重要的是你是
able to look in this folder and find a
能够在此文件夹中查找并找到
specific painting very easily based on
特定的绘画很容易基于
the name and date to learn more about
要了解更多信息的名称和日期
file organization I have a reference
档案组织我有一个推荐人
video you can watch those were some of
你可以观看这些视频中的一些
the basic functions and skills you'll be
你将具备的基本职能和技能
learning in CR in our next lesson we
在我们的下一课中学习CR
will be exploring what we can do with
将会探索我们能做些什么
the tools and some of their controls in
中的工具及其一些控件
the tool
工具
options
选项